Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Executive Office Records, 1951-1999
  - Subseries II:B: Lillian Roberts Associate Director Records, 1951-1983.
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals I, 1967-1972; cuid4616 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals II, 1967-1972; cuid4617 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Career Development and Training: Hospitals III, 1967-1972; cuid4618 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Carver Federal Savings: Board of Directors, 1974-1981; cuid4619 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Career Programs, 1970-1972; cuid4620 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974; cuid4621 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Dec 1974-May 1975; cuid4622 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Clerical-Administrative Division: Monthly Reports, Jun 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4623 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 1973-1979; cuid4624 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Coalition of Concerned Citizens for Human Resources, 1974-1976; cuid4625 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Coalition of Trade Union Women, 1974-1978; cuid4626 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - College of New Rochelle DC 37 Campus, New Resources Program, 1973-1975, 1978; cuid4627 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents, undated, 1975-1976; cuid4628 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Committee of Interns and Residents: Effects of Personnel Reductions in Hospitals, 1978; cuid4629 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Committee to Aid the Refugees of East Pakistan, 1971; cuid4630 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Community Mental Health Center, 1973-1974; cuid4631 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Community School Board Elections, 1974-1975; cuid4632 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA), Oct 1978-Apr 1979; cuid4633 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - CETA, May 1979-Jun 1979; cuid4634 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - CETA, Jul 1979-Aug 1979; cuid4635 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - CETA, Sep 1979; cuid4636 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - CETA, Oct 1979-Mar 1980; cuid4637 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - CETA Questionnaire, 1979; cuid4638 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Contracting Out: Hospitals, 1975; cuid4639 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1970; cuid4640 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1971-Dec 1971; cuid4641 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1972-Mar 1972; cuid4642 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Apr 10, 1972-Jun 1972; cuid4643 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1972-Oct 1972; cuid4644 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1972-Dec 1972; cuid4645 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1973-Jun 1973; cuid4646 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1973-Dec 1973; cuid4647 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1974-May 1974; cuid4648 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1974-Dec 1974; cuid4649 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1975; cuid4650 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1977-Jun 1977; cuid4651 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4652 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1978-Mar 1978; cuid4653 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1978-May 1978; cuid4654 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1978; cuid4655 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Jul 1978-Dec 1978; cuid4656 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1979-May 1979; cuid4657 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1979-Sep 1979; cuid4658 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1979-Dec 1979; cuid4659 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1980; cuid4660 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1981-Feb 1981; cuid4661 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1981-Jun 1981; cuid4662 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Coney Island Hospital, 1976-1979; cuid4663 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA): Clerical Division, ca.1975; cuid4664 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Council for the Advancement of Experiential Learning (CAEL), 1977-1980; cuid4665 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Cumberland Hospital, 1975-1978; cuid4666 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Cumberland Hospital Mental Health Service, 1974; cuid4667 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Daycare Programs, 1970-1972; cuid4668 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Delafield Hospital: Action to Prevent Closing, 1975; cuid4669 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Delafield Hospital: Legal Papers, 1975; cuid4670 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976; cuid4671 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Democratic National Party Conference: Platform Advisory Committee, 1979; cuid4672 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Education Fund, 1970-1971; cuid4673 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Education Fund, 1976-1979; cuid4674 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Educational Guidance Center for the Retarded, 1971; cuid4675 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 I, 1971-1974; cuid4676 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Emergency Employment Act of 1971 II, 1971-1974; cuid4677 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Emergency Medical Services: Safety Conditions and Training, 1972-1976; cuid4678 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Executive Staff, 1972; cuid4679 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1969-1972; cuid4680 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Federation of Field Representatives, 1975-1981; cuid4681 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Federation of Field Representatives: Agreements, 1970-1980; cuid4682 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Feed the Hungry Drive, 1974; cuid4683 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Budget Meetings with City Departments, 1976; cuid4684 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Fordham Hospital, undated, 1976; cuid4685 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Ghetto Medicine Program (New York State), 1977-1978; cuid4686 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Goldwater Hospital Parking Facility Closing, 1973-1974; cuid4687 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1975-1976; cuid4688 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Gouverneur Hospital, 1977-1978; cuid4689 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Harlem Hospital, 1975-1979; cuid4690 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Harlem Hospital: Community-Worker Board, 1969; cuid4691 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Health and Security Plan: Option IV, 1976-1978; cuid4692 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Help Our Own Fund (for laid-off members), 1975-1976; cuid4693 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - High Risk Premature Infant Technician Training Program, 1970-1971; cuid4694 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - HIP of Greater New York, 1972; cuid4695 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Home Attendants, 1977-1978; cuid4696 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Closings and Layoffs, 1976; cuid4697 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Hospitals Division: Monthly Reports, Apr 1974-Nov 1974; cuid4698 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Housekeeping Aid Sanitation Training Program, 1971-1972; cuid4699 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - I Paid My Dues (labor play), 1976; cuid4700 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - International Conference on Trends in Industrial Relations (Tel Aviv, Israel), 1971; cuid4701 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Interns, 1972; cuid4702 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Invitations, 1970-1971; cuid4703 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Just One Break (JOB), 1977; cuid4704 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - King, Martin Luther, Jr.: DC 37 Response to Assassination and Tributes, 1968-1978; cuid4705 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Kings County Hospital Center, 1973-1978; cuid4706 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Kings County Hospital Center: Attitudinal Program, 1972; cuid4707 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Legal Internship and Training Education (LITE) Program: Bedford Stuyvesant Lawyers Association, 1977-1978; cuid4708 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Legal Services Proposal, 1972; cuid4709 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Legislative Information, 1969-1971, 1978; cuid4710 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Lincoln Hospital, 1971-1978; cuid4711 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Local 154 (Amalgamated Professional Employees), 1979-1980; cuid4712 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1969-1971; cuid4713 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Local 371(SSEU), 1975-1976; cuid4714 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Local 371 (SSEU), 1977-1981; cuid4715 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Contract, 1969-1970; cuid4716 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Dental Assistants, 1968-1971; cuid4717 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Local 371 (SSEU): Homemakers and Housekeepers, 1968-1971; cuid4718 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1970-1971; cuid4719 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1975; cuid4720 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education), 1976-1981; cuid4721 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Career Training Programs, 1970-1971; cuid4722 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Hourly Workers, 1970-1971; cuid4723 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): New York Archdiocese Schools, 1970-1971; cuid4724 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Local 372 (Board of Education): Para-Professionals, 1969; cuid4725 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Local 374 (Quasi-Public Employees), 1978; cuid4726 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1975-1976; cuid4727 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Local 375 (CSTG), 1977-1980; cuid4728 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Local 384 (CUNY): Gittelson Employees, 1951-1980; cuid4729 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1966-1967; cuid4730 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1968-Apr 1968; cuid4731 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), May 1968-Jul 1968; cuid4732 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Aug 1968-Dec 1968; cuid4733 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jan 1969-May 1969; cuid4734 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Jun 1969-Dec 1969; cuid4735 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1970; cuid4736 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975; cuid4737 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1975-1976; cuid4738 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), 1977-Aug 1980; cuid4739 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union), Sep 1980-Apr 1981; cuid4740 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Ambulance Technicians, 1969-1972; cuid4741 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, 1978-1980; cuid4742 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): James Butler Dispute, Petitions and Legal Papers, 1978-1979; cuid4743 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Bonano v. Butler, Release Time Information, 1976-1979; cuid4744 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election I, 1980; cuid4745 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Delegates Election II, 1980; cuid4746 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Dietary Aide Training Program, 1968-1971; cuid4747 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): History, 1974; cuid4748 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Mortuary Caretakers, 1974-1975; cuid4749 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Roosevelt Island Parking, 1973-1977; cuid4750 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Local 420 (Municipal Hospital Employees Union): Uniform Committee, 1970-1972; cuid4751 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Local 768 (Health Services Employees), 1979-1980; cuid4752 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Local 957 (New York City Housing Authority Clericals), 1975-1979; cuid4753 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Local 1070 (Court, County and Department of Probation Employees), 1973-1977; cuid4754 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Local 1219 (Real Estate Employees): Housing Relocation Aides, 1971, 1978; cuid4755 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Local 1321 (Queens Library Guild), 1976; cuid4756 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Local 1359 (Rent Regulation Services Employees), 1980; cuid4757 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Local 1457 (Juvenile Center): Counselors, 1970, 1977-1980; cuid4758 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees), 1969-1971; cuid4759 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Fort Greene Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4760 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Hunts Point Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4761 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Lower West Side Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4762 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Qualicap's Health and Welfare Action Center, 1970; cuid4763 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Bronx Community Corporation, 1969-1970; cuid4764 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): South Brooklyn and Red Hook Community Corporations, 1969-1970; cuid4765 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Local 1485 (Anti-Poverty Employees): Southeast Queens Community Corporation, 1970; cuid4766 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Local 1503 (Metropolitan Museum of Art), 1979; cuid4767 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Local 1509 (Youth Board Employees), 1972-1980; cuid4768 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees), undated, 1978-1981; cuid4769 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Local 1549 (Clerical-Administrative Employees): Police Department, 1977-1980; cuid4770 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Local 1597 (Custodial Assistant Employees), 1972-1980; cuid4771 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Local 1931 (TBTA Maintenance Employees), 1980-1981; cuid4772 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Local 2021 (Off-Track Betting Corporation, OTB), Dec 1974-Mar 1975; cuid4773 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), Apr 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4774 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Local 2021 (OTB), 1976-1979; cuid4775 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1970-1973; cuid4776 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1974-1976; cuid4777 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Local 2507 (Ambulance Corpsmen), 1977-1980; cuid4778 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Local 2627 (New York City Electronic Data Processing Employees), 1978-1980; cuid4779 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - March on Washington (labor coalition), 1975; cuid4780 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Mayor's Midtown Citizens Committee, 1976; cuid4781 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Medical Surgical Technician Training Program, 1971; cuid4782 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Membership Gain/Loss Records and Dues Check-off Reports, 1969-1972; cuid4783 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Methadone Maintenance Treatment Program, 1971; cuid4784 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Metropolitan Hospital, 1979; cuid4785 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Minority Advisory Committee to Secretary of U. S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1978; cuid4786 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Mobilization for Youth: "Establishing a New Career, The Social Health Technician", 1970; cuid4787 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Mobilization for Youth: New Occupations Demonstration Project, 1969; cuid4788 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Mobilization for Youth: Social Health and Psychiatric Technician Training Program, 1970-1971; cuid4789 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Morrisania City Hospital, 1976-1977; cuid4790 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1974-Jun 1977; cuid4791 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Municipal Credit Union, Jul 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4792 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Municipal Credit Union, 1978; cuid4793 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Municipal Credit Union: Advisory Committee, 1978-1979; cuid4794 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Municipal Employees Legal Service Fund (MELS), 1973-1980; cuid4795 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - National Association of Health Services Executives, 1977; cuid4796 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - National Child Labor Committee: Board of Trustees, 1979-1980; cuid4797 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - National Science Foundation Research Project: "Relations Among Work Organization, Job Satisfaction, and Productivity", 1973-1974; cuid4798 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" I, 1979; cuid4799 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - New York City: "A Plan for Improving the Effectiveness of Hospital Services…" II, 1979; cuid4800 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - New York City: "Plan for Localized Government", 1972; cuid4801 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - New York City Agency for Child Development, 1971-1974; cuid4802 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - New York City Board of Education: Addiction Prevention Program Instructors (Local 372), 1974-1975; cuid4803 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - New York City Department of Hospitals, 1967; cuid4804 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, 1969-1970; cuid4805 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, 1971; cuid4806 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, 1972-1974; cuid4807 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1975-Jun 1975; cuid4808 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jul 1975-Dec 1975; cuid4809 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1976-Mar 1976; cuid4810 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1976-May 1976; cuid4811 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1976-Aug 1976; cuid4812 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC, Sep 1976-Dec 1976; cuid4813 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1977-May 1977; cuid4814 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1977-Oct 1977; cuid4815 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1977-Dec 1977; cuid4816 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1978-Apr 1978; cuid4817 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC, May 1978-Sep 1978; cuid4818 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC, Oct 1978-Dec 1978; cuid4819 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1979; cuid4820 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC, Feb 1979-Mar 1979; cuid4821 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC, Apr 1979; cuid4822 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC, May 1979; cuid4823 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1979-Jul 1979; cuid4824 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC, Aug 1979-Oct 1979; cuid4825 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1979-Dec 1979; cuid4826 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC, Jan 1980-Feb 1980; cuid4827 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC, Mar 1980-May 1980; cuid4828 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC, Jun 1980-Oct 1980; cuid4829 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC, Nov 1980-Dec 1980; cuid4830 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC, 1981; cuid4831 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Ad Hoc Panel on Threatened Strike ("Patterson Panel" and Tri-Partite Task Force on Proposed Layoffs), 1976; cuid4832 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1968-Feb 1971; cuid4833 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Mar 1971-1972; cuid4834 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, 1973-1975; cuid4835 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Jul 1970-Feb 1972; cuid4836 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Contracts and Financial Records, Apr 1972-Apr 1975; cuid4837 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, 1974-Apr 1975; cuid4838 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Crisis Budget Information, undated, May 1975-Sep 1975; cuid4839 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Employee List, ca.1972; cuid4840 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Affiliation of Municipal and Voluntary Hospitals, Publicity, 1972-1975; cuid4841 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Affirmative Action Plan, 1973-1974; cuid4842 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Bellevue Hospital Labor/Management Productivity Committee Report, 1977; cuid4843 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Board of Directors (Budget crisis), 1975; cuid4844 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Bronx Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1975; cuid4845 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Hospitals (Budget crisis), 1974; cuid4846 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Brooklyn Regionalization Program, 1977-1980; cuid4847 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, 1974-1975; cuid4848 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Budget Crisis, CHP Reports, 1975; cuid4849 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Clerical Division, 1970-1971; cuid4850 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Clippings, 1970-1975; cuid4851 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Community Boards, 1970-1971; cuid4852 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1973-1974; cuid4853 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1976; cuid4854 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Education and Training, 1977-1978; cuid4855 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Education Programs, 1972-1975; cuid4856 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Emergency Medical Service (EMS), 1977; cuid4857 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: EMS, 1978; cuid4858 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: EMS Manhattan Plan, 1978-1982; cuid4859 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - New York City HHC: Ethnic Census, 1970; cuid4860 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - New York City HHC: Financial Plan Data, 1978; cuid4861 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - New York City HHC: Functional Program and Space Utilization Study, 1976; cuid4862 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - New York City HHC: Gouverneur Hospital Closing, 1976; cuid4863 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Aug 1976-Mar 1977; cuid4864 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - New York City HHC: Joint Labor-Management Productivity Committee, Apr 1977-Sep 1978; cuid4865 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - New York City HHC: Labor-Management Conferences, 1970-1971; cuid4866 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - New York City HHC: Layoff Analysis, 1976; cuid4867 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - New York City HHC: Medicaid Reimbursements (New York State Office of Health Systems Management), 1978; cuid4868 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - New York City HHC: Patient Accounting Proposal, 1977; cuid4869 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel and Layoffs, 1975; cuid4870 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - New York City HHC: Personnel Review Board Decisions, 1978-1979; cuid4871 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - New York City HHC: Press Releases, 1970-1977; cuid4872 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) I, 1977-1978; cuid4873 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Committee, Cost of Living Adjustment (COLA) II, 1977-1978; cuid4874 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Program, 1977; cuid4875 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1976-1977; cuid4876 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - New York City HHC: Productivity Working Papers, 1978; cuid4877 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - New York City HHC: Professional Division (Local 1407), 1970; cuid4878 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - New York City HHC: Rollbacks, 1967-1973; cuid4879 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - New York City HHC: Roosevelt Island Laundry Closing, 1974-1975; cuid4880 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - New York City HHC: Taylor Law Application (1976 Strike), 1970, 1976-1978; cuid4881 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - New York City HHC: Training Coalition, 1970-1971; cuid4882 (Box 24, Folder 9)